This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
You really did it!
You're awesome, Mr.
Bass!
I can't believe we're friends with
the outlaw to save the city, Clay!
Oh yeah, he's a dangerous
criminal, ain't he, huh?
Come on, Trico!
Hi, so are you enjoying your drink?
Yes, very much.
Thanks for asking.
Yes, I'm drinking.
That Bash the Stampede really
is an unusual guy, isn't he?
I mean, sure, everybody's a lot less
tense now that the plant is fixed.
But those are the very same people
that tried to kill him for the reward.
You think he might be more
uncomfortable around them.
Trouble seems to follow
him wherever he goes.
I think the world would be a lot
better and safer place without him.
Don't worry, I can't handle it.
I am unique and eat anything I want to.
I'll have a separate stomach
just for cake and ice cream.
Your friend is another unusual one.
It's no good, Henry.
He's completely out of
it, dead to the world.
Guess I gave him a
little too much to drink.
I'm sorry I called you
both out here for nothing.
I didn't think he'd pass out.
Be sure to say hi to Sylvie for me.
It's really too bad, isn't it?
You don't get a chance to sleep
with a guy like that every day.
Well, see you around. Bye.
Could I be regretting it?
Just a little?
What?
Vash is leaving?
But he didn't even say goodbye.
Hurry up, Millie!
He just told me. that Mr.
Vash got on the sand steamer
But we don't have enough money.
Vash wait
Hey!
Hey, you better come
back and see me sometime!
How could you just leave
without saying goodbye?
Be good to your mom and
stay out of trouble, Taunus!
Goodbye!
Bye!
Bye! See ya!
Alright!
At long last I am finally on my own again!
I think I drank too much!
You bash the stampede?
You sure don't look like it.
I didn't call anyone for room service.
We're about to go into Latenburg Canyon.
Yeah, and?
You have heard of it, haven't you?
It's the turf of the biggest,
baddest, most notorious gang around.
The bad lad thieves.
If I can get you on guard duty,
I can charge double the fare, and
we'll both make some good money.
Say you'll do it.
Now, see here.
Huh?
I am a simple passenger.
My life, my safety is depending
on your ship's defenses.
So don't let me down.
Hey, hey, come on!
Geez.
I sure wish I had chosen
a quieter way to travel.
Now to catch some more Z's.
Oh, shit!
Hold it!
Right there!
Don't you know when you hurt somebody
that you're supposed to apologize?
Look at this! I'm bleeding!
You got that when you're bashed
through the vent, you big idiot!
Huh?
What's this supposed to be,
some kind of stranglehold?
You can't hurt me while
you're up in the air, kid.
You're a stowaway, aren't you? Uh-huh.
That's right, I am.
My parents died when I was real young,
so I went to live with
some distant relatives,
but it was so horrible
there I couldn't stand it.
My grandmother would get
drunk and hit me all the time,
and my weird uncle was really mean.
He was always trying to get at me.
If I can just get to me, I can escape
them if I have to go back to that place
I don't know what they'll do to me.
Please mister.
Please don't don't turn me in
Boy, I'm dead nobody's dumb
enough to buy such a lame story.
It's the worst one I've ever come up with
It's all right,
I understand it must
have been so hard don't
worry I'll protect you
whoa is this guy for real
that's two bacon lettuce
dogs two cartons of
milk wait a minute four
bags of pretzels and
one pack of raisins I
must say I am very curious
as to why you insurance
girls are here doing
this work care to let me in on it well we
didn't have enough money
for a ticket so we got a
part-time job here all
together that It comes
to twelve double dollars
and seventy-five C cents.
Uh, okay.
I'm amazed that you're still so hungry
after just having finished your dinner.
You have an appetite
just like a growing boy.
Think so?
Geez, those girls are pretty sharp.
The big one is exceptionally scary.
My only salvation is she
doesn't know how smart she is.
Hey, Vash!
Guard this place well.
It wasn't easy to get
you that room, you know.
You got it
Hello there growing boy.
I'm back
Your mouth may be silent,
but your eyes speak real loud
and clear saying I'm starving
It's really dark out there,
not a single light to be seen.
Oh yeah?
It'll be bright soon enough.
Sorry about that Mr. Goody Goody.
One more left. I gotta hurry.
Hey, bear me. Yeah?
What's our time?
Two, two, five, three.
Okay.
Listen up.
The kids should have it all set by now.
Seven minutes to parade time,
make it good and flashy.
Right on time!
It's the purple signal!
All right, let's do it!
Here we go!
Oh, no! Captain!
What is it?
Oh, my God! Let's go!
It's the Bad Man King.
What the hell is going on up there?
Bastards!
Even jerks!
I don't understand.
What's the big man doing?
I thought he was getting
paid, so this doesn't happen.
Why aren't the main cannons firing?
I tried, sir.
They're not responding.
What's happening?
What's going on?
We're under attack!
They're on the starboard rear hatch!
Ah, the magnificent dreadnought raiders.
I, leader of the bad lads,
personally trained them.
Brilliant dynamite's neon now emerges.
to take over.
Now, my friends, it's harvest time.
What glitters on this ship belongs to me.
You performed brilliantly, kid.
Nice job.
Now gather all the passengers in one spot
and take me to the party room. Right.
Yes, sir.
It's a song.
I hear a song.
The second evening,
where the children love them, have all
joined hands and composed for more.
You know, I'm so excited!
The meaning of life?
You're a very serious
mind, aren't you, Bash?
We decide our own destinies.
Rem.
You're such a baby.
Our tickets to the future are open.
Please, decide your own destiny.
Rem!
Don't leave yet! Rem!
WAIT!
What is that?
Meow!
Junk!
Is that all you got?
Pathetic beggars?
What do you think, I'm stupid?
Hey, boss!
Well now, there it is.
And it's a big one.
Very nice.
Open it up for me, would you?
It's impossible.
I couldn't do it even if I wanted to.
There isn't a single person on this ship
who knows a combination to that safe.
Besides, the only coded key is
carefully locked away in the city.
I swear it's not here!
I see.
Thanks for the information.
That means we'll just
have to break it open.
Once we have made our way around the
mountain to the right, then go straight.
In five, take a northeast course
and stay within sight of the canyon.
Then begin to accelerate.
At full speed, we will arrive
in just about ten minutes.
This is our destination the
Anora precipice what well at
least let me release the
passengers please sir we risked
our lives to get here it's
only fair that you should
be expected to risk your
lives too depraved mad lunatic
the Super Express will take
your lives out in a blaze
of glory if it's not flashing
in high style what's the
point this is a horrible
mess we're in Meryl we're
gonna need a lot more than
just the two of us to take on
a gang that's so heavily armed
the only person who could
do something in a situation
like this is him although
I hate to admit it I can't
even believe I just said
that my neck hurts I have
absolutely no idea where I am?
Neil boy, isn't that the break?
Did you actually think I wouldn't notice?
Everyone on this crew is sworn to
protect the passengers at any cost.
I can't good conscience go against that.
I'll honor that even if I have to die.
Have it your way.
No!
Such a waste.
You have the stuff pros are made of.
I think I'll preserve you just like
you are while you're still beautiful.
No, don't! Stop it!
I got the kid!
Go on, move it!
Now now don't look so
grim, little partner.
Adults are prone to many
unhappy differences of opinion.
I brought you up here
because I wanted to see
if you knew how to
steer this huge clunker.
I don't know the layout of the console,
but you need to regulate
the amount of co2 sent to
the heating plant and monitor
the stress on the boiler.
The light and heat on the hydro plant also
needs to be regulated
and monitored constantly.
It's important to have experience.
Who the hell is that boy?
So what you're saying is this
thing is a pain in the ass?
Guess I shouldn't have
killed the poor bastard.
Hey, what's so important
about the steering?
I mean, it's been
exhilarating, kind of funny.
So?
So why don't you just take
the goods and split now?
Well, because the plan has changed.
The swag of the day is in the huge
safe in the middle of the ship.
A lot tougher than the usual
crappy safes we run into.
The worst part of it is that we have
milky unless we go into the city.
Isn't it sad enough to
make you want to cry?
Tell me, what would you do?
Your response?
You cracked the whole thing in half.
What's wrong?
I'll do anything you want.
I'll do anything you want,
but just not that. Huh?
You never said you were gonna do that.
I was only supposed to
silence the security
guards to let you and the bad lads inside.
So why is it now we're wrecking the
whole sand steamer all of a sudden?
Why?
That was never part of our deal.
I can't allow it.
Hey, kid.
Are you misunderstanding something here?
I won the goods on this ship, so why
the hell would I have to answer to you?
Before I collect what's already mine!
Kid, you ain't being beautiful.
If you're gonna use your knowledge of
the ship for a trade with the bad guys,
at least prepare for the worst,
stupid.
Please, you gotta leave the ship alone!
Boy, don't be a fool!
Shut up and do what he says!
Never!
This ship belongs to my father!
It's not yours!
This ship belongs to my dad!
Dad!
Enough.
This isn't fun anymore.
Splatter time.
You okay, Squirt? Over here.
Don't move now, or you'll get hurt.
Boss, Samson was in the passenger cabin!
Who the hell is that?
This'll be fun.
Hey, scumbags! Yeah!
Vest me a souvenir! Yes, sir!
Make it something beautiful and gorgeous!
Yeah!
Hey, couldn't you think of
a better way to rescue me?
This sucks, big time!
Don't be so ungrateful, kid!
Besides, I received a heck of
a lot more damage than you did!
If we climb a little higher, we
can get to a ventilation shaft.
Okay, let's get going.
I mean, like, let's get going right away.
Oh, it's a warehouse.
Huh? What's this?
Looks like trunks.
Sorry about hitting you like
I did, Captain. Forgive me.
It looks like I can't quite control
the ship without your help after all.
So this time, to make it
easier for you to steer,
I enlisted a volunteer from
the passengers for inspiration.
No!
Shit! You are sick!
Just go to hell and die!
I'm getting kind of tired
of being told to do that.
Let me go!
You're looking in the wrong direction.
The control lever is right over there.
It's your ship.
You should be the one
to break the bad news.
At least you'll be going down
with it like a good captain.
You only have one thing to do.
Speed it up.
people who sin say this
that they had to to
survive people who sin
say this it's too late
now to stop a shadow called sin dogs them
steadily from behind
silently without a word
remorse and agony are
repeated only to end up at
despair in the end but the
sinners just don't know
that if they'd only turn
around there's a light there
a light which keeps shining
on them ever so lonely,
a light that will never fade.